

## TO

Shawna Speake
Human Resources &
Office Administrator

Belmont Nursery 7730 E Belmont Ave. Fresno, CA 93737

**Date** 01 July 2021

# Will Christensen

## **COVER LETTER**

Dear Shawna Speake,

After a discussion with Jon Reelhorn earlier this week, I've become incredibly excited about the position of Inventory Specialist at Belmont Nursery. As an Ag Business major with professional experience in logistics, quality assurance, data analysis, account management and a personal passion for horticulture, I am confident that I would be a valuable and immediate asset to the Belmont Nursery team.

As an Operations Analytical Coordinator at West Pak Avocado, I developed a deep understanding of the logistics, QA and coordination it takes to succeed in a rapidly growing, high demand Agricultural business. I am convinced that this vital skillset, paired with the Account Management and Customer service expertise I developed during my time at Catalyst Marketing will empower me to excel as an Inventory Specialist at Belmont Nursery.

I would sincerely appreciate the opportunity to speak with you regarding this position. Thank you for your consideration; I hope to hear from you soon.

Best Regards,
Will Christensen
William Christensen



## CONTACT

**②** 4

4572 Round MTN Lane, Sanger

559-284-4414

willmchristensen@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

## Agricultural Business

California Polytechnic University / San Luis Obispo 2014 - 2019

### **SKILLS**

#### //Professional

Transportation & Logistics
Quality Assurance
Inventory Management
Sales & Marketing
Account Management
Horticulture & Crop Science
Irrigation Water Management
SOP & ISO Creation
Ag Personnel Management
Customer Service

#### //Technical

Microsoft Office
Adobe Photoshop
Java
Famous Software
Advanced Excel Skills
(Expertise in Logistical Analysis)

### Hobbies

Reading Yoga
Gardening Exercise
Cooking Outdoors
Hiking Climbing
Golfing Photography

# Will Christensen

Experienced Logistical & QA analyst with a passion for Horticulture

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Instacart / Full Service Shopper

Feb 2021 - Present Fresno, California, United States Role/Responsibilities:

Used the Instacart platform as an independent contractor to shop for and deliver orders to my customers.

- Shopping: Handle exchanges and returns through the application by following set protocols and regulations. Developed thorough understanding of the inner workings(layout, pricing, product availability) of grocery stores throughout the central valley.
- Customer Service: Maintained an average customer approval rating of 99.4% //
  (4.97 stars) after over 140 completed batches. Provided exceptional customer
  service according to the taste and preferences of each app user. Completed multiple
  orders in a single batch while maintaining exceptional order accuracy and speed.

#### ) Sprouts / Deli Clerk

Aug 2020 - Feb 2021 7477 N Blackstone Ave, Fresno, CA 93720 Role/Responsibilities:

- Open Hours: Providing unparalleled customer service whilst managing and maintaining day-to-day tasks.
- Closed Hours: Preparing the department for the morning shift by independently closing the sandwich bar and deli production area.
- Customer Service: Preparing, packaging, and pricing meat, cheese, and meals according to customers' preferences.

## Catalyst Marketing Company/ Account Coordinator

Jan 2020 - July 2020

1466 Van Ness Ave, Fresno, CA 93721

Role/Responsibilities:

- **Key Account Manager:** Worked closely with colleagues to ensure the success of key accounts through effective stakeholder management & on-time delivery of exceptional products/services.
- Marketing Manager: Ideated developed and optimized successful marketing campaigns spanning a variety of marketing channels including physical advertisement, on-site web design, video & branding / "tone of voice" for key accounts.

#### Accounts & Accomplishments:

Marketing Event Coordinator: Planned, coordinated, & executed weekly/monthly marketing events for Soaring Eagle Casino & Resort and Selma Auto Mall resulting in increased revenue, new customers & retention of their current client base.

**Visit Las Cruces:** Ideated, pitch, and won RFP, developed rebranding campaign (tracked by a variety of KPI metrics to ensure proper results of the rebrand).

Central Valley Caregivers Association: Rebranding campaign that involved the development and design of an entirely new website, including video content and copy. Multiple logo concepts drawn and revised according to client's tastes and preferences.

#### Operations Analytical Coordinator / West Pak Avocado Inc.

Aug 2019 - Jan 2020 38655 Sky Canyon Dr, Murrieta, CA 92563 Role/Responsibilities:

- Logistics, Inventory & QA Manager: Responsible for the coordination, organization, and quality assurance of all avocado shipping/receiving.
- Data Analyst: Responsible for creating and presenting comprehensive MOM / YOY analysis of core KPI's for the production, shipment and receiving of all product inventory utilizing Excel Pivot Tables.
- Key Account Manager: Coordinated with multiple teams + VP level management to ensure the success of key accounts like Target, Sam's Club/Costco, Walmart, Sprouts Farmers Market, Ralphs.

## REFERENCES

Trevor Newhouse

West Pak Avocado/ VP of Operations

Phone: (951) 296-5757

**Andrew Astone** 

Catalyst Marketing / Account Leader

Phone: (559)-252-2500